Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files K-O, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files L
    - La Barrie, Lillian (Box A-71, Folder 140)
    - La Beach, Byron (Box A-71, Folder 141)
      Photographer if identified: M Associates
    - La Beach, Lloyd (Box A-71, Folder 142)
      Photographer if identified: Pan American
    - La Beach Food Co. (Box A-71, Folder 143)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Alex Summers
    - LaBelle, Patti (Box A-71, Folder 144)
      Photographer if identified: Edward Reed
    - LaBelle, Patti (Box A-71, Folder 145)
      Photographer if identified: K. Jewell, Norman Frederick, Bryan D. Hall, Pictorial Enterprise, James J. Kriegsmann, Bob Gruen,
    - LaBelle, Patti (Box A-71, Folder 146)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Juanita M. Cole, Gene Bagnato
    - Labor Day '85 (Box A-71, Folder 147)
      Photographer if identified: Lem Peterkin
    - Labor Day 1986 Eastern Parkway (Box A-71, Folder 148)
    - Labor Supplement 1979 (Box A-71, Folder 149)
      Also 2 newspaper photos.
      Photographer if identified: Standard Studios, Pictorial Enterprise, Al Ben-Ness, Ed Snider, David Adler, James Gilbert,
    - La Brew, Arthur (Box A-71, Folder 150)
    - La Caille, Rupert A. Dr. (Box A-71, Folder 151)
    - Lacayo, Hortensia (Box A-71, Folder 152)
    - Lacefield, Jean (Box A-71, Folder 153)
    - Lacefield, Reggie (Box A-71, Folder 154)
    - Lacey, Celia (Box A-71, Folder 155)
      Photographer if identified: Smith
    - Lacey, Diane (Box A-71, Folder 156)
      Also one velox print. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Blackstone-Shelburne, A. Hansen, Newell Johnson, Harris Photo,
    - Lacey, James (Box A-71, Folder 157)
    - Lacey, Pat (Box A-71, Folder 158)
    - Lacks, JoAnn (Box A-71, Folder 159)
    - La Crosse Players (Box A-71, Folder 160)
    - Lacy, Connie (Box A-71, Folder 161)
    - Lacy, Florence E. (Box A-71, Folder 162)
    - Lacy, Jack (Box A-71, Folder 163)
      Photographer if identified: Popsie
    - Lacy, Margaret (Box A-71, Folder 164)
    - Lacy, Stanhope (Box A-71, Folder 165)
    - Ladd, Ernie (Box A-71, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: Robert W. Cottrol
    - Ladebo, Ladi (Box A-71, Folder 167)
      Also one velox print. 1 print has caption stapled to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo,
    - Ladies and Gentlemen...F360 (Box A-71, Folder 168)
    - Ladies Honorary Auxiliary (Box A-71, Folder 169)
    - Ladler, George (Box A-71, Folder 170)
    - Ladner, Joyce (Box A-71, Folder 171)
    - La Doll Venus, Mary Smith & Janie Mickens (Box A-71, Folder 172)
    - Ladsen, Etta (Box A-71, Folder 173)
    - Ladson, Andrea (Box A-71, Folder 174)
    - Ladson, Cleveland (Box A-71, Folder 175)
    - Ladson, Etta (Box A-71, Folder 176)
    - Ladson, John P. (Rev.) (Box A-71, Folder 177)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes, Bro. David McAdams,
    - Ladson, Leroy (Box A-71, Folder 178)
    - Ladson, Sallie (Mrs.) (Box A-71, Folder 179)
    - Lady Bishop (Box A-71, Folder 180)
      Ms. note and envelope attached to print with paper clip.
    - "Lady C" (Box A-71, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: Cleveland Davies
    - Lady's Say (Renee Minus White) (Box A-71, Folder 182)
      Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson
    - La Farge, John (Father) (Box A-71, Folder 183)
      Also 1 envelope of 6"x6" negatives dated 2-25-1952 by Smith. 1 strip, 2 images. "Dinner for Father La Farge Hotel Waldorf Astoria"
      Photographer if identified: Arnold C. DeMille,
    - La Farge, Oliver (Box A-71, Folder 184)
    - Lafayette, Bernard (Box A-71, Folder 185)
      Photographer if identified: S.C.L.C.
    - Lafayette Theater (Box A-71, Folder 186)
      Also 1 envelope with 1 4"x5" negative by Dummett, dated 1-11-1952, "Lafayette Bldg future home of Williams Institute." 1 envelope with 1 4"x5" negative by Dummett, dated 3-22-1948, "Lafayette Theater."
    - Laffin, Charles W. Jr. Dr. (Box A-71, Folder 187)
    - La Follette, Charles M (Box A-71, Folder 188)
    - La Fontaine, Rosella (Box A-71, Folder 189)
    - LaFontant, Jewel S. (Box A-71, Folder 190)
      Photographer if identified: TWA Public Relations
    - La Forest, Neil (Box A-71, Folder 191)
    - Laforte, Ginger (Mrs.) (Box A-71, Folder 192)
    - Latouche, John (Box A-71, Folder 193)
    - La Fourche, James S. (Box A-71, Folder 194)
    - La France, Audrey (Box A-71, Folder 195)
    - La Franque, Adele (Box A-71, Folder 196)
    - Lagrone, Oliver (Box A-71, Folder 197)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorello (Mayor) (Box A-71, Folder 198)
    - LaGuardia, Mrs. Marie (Box A-71, Folder 199)
    - Laguna, Ismael (Box A-71, Folder 200)
    - Laidley, Tony (Box A-71, Folder 201)
    - Laine, Cleo (Box A-71, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: V.J. Ryan
    - Laine, Frankie (Box A-71, Folder 203)
    - Laing, Dr. Clarence (Box A-71, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Elson-Alexandre
    - Laing, Leslie (Box A-71, Folder 205)
      Photographer if identified: Enell Inc.
    - Laird, Melvin (Box A-71, Folder 206)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Dept. of Defense/David B. WIlson
    - Lake, Conrad (Box A-71, Folder 207)
      Photographer if identified: Port Authority of NY/NJ
    - Lake, Diana (Box A-71, Folder 208)
    - Lake, Mya (Box A-71, Folder 209)
      Photographer if identified: Big M Photo Service
    - Lake, Neville B. (Box A-71, Folder 210)
    - Lake, Oliver (Box A-71, Folder 211)
      Photographer if identified: Studio One,
    - Lake, Sarah V. (Box A-71, Folder 212)
      Photographer if identified: NY Daily News Photo
    - Lake, Sidney (Dr.) (Box A-71, Folder 213)
      Print mounted on cardboard.
    - Lake, Sophronia Verge (Box A-71, Folder 214)
      Photographer if identified: John Bowen
    - Lake, Thelma & Sylvia (Box A-71, Folder 215)
    - Lake, William J. (Box A-71, Folder 216)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Cooper
    - Lakers (Box A-71, Folder 217)
    - Lakeside (Box A-71, Folder 218)
      Photographer if identified: Scott Hensel
    - La King, Rosa (Box A-71, Folder 219)
    - LaZard, Jack (Box A-71, Folder 220)
    - Marie-Claude Lalique (Box A-71, Folder 221)
      Also press release, newspaper clippings.
    - La Lupe (Box A-71, Folder 222)
      Photographer if identified: Jos. Abeles
    - LaMar, Cheri (Box A-71, Folder 223)
    - Damon D. LaMar (Box A-71, Folder 224)
    - Lamar, Jacob (Box A-71, Folder 225)
    - LaMar, La Reine (Box A-71, Folder 226)
    - LaMar, La Reine (Box A-71, Folder 227)
    - Lamar, Ralph (Box A-71, Folder 228)
    - LaMar, Rence (Box A-71, Folder 229)
    - LaMarr, Kelly (Box A-71, Folder 230)
    - Lamb, Mr. & Mrs. George (Box A-71, Folder 231)
    - Lamb, Gerald (Box A-71, Folder 232)
    - Lamb, John (Box A-71, Folder 233)
    - Lamb, Leroy (Box A-71, Folder 234)
    - Lamb, Peter (Box A-71, Folder 235)
    - Lambay, George (Box A-71, Folder 236)
    - Lambda Kappa Mu Sorors (Box A-71, Folder 237)
      Also one velox print. 2 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Alex Summers, Brooks-La Couche, King Photographers,
    - Lambe, Joseph (Box A-71, Folder 238)
    - Lambert, Adelle (Box A-71, Folder 239)
    - Lambert, Arthur (Box A-71, Folder 240)
    - Lambert, Celester (Box A-71, Folder 241)
    - Lambert, Deatra (Box A-71, Folder 242)
    - Lambert, Elba (Box A-71, Folder 243)
    - Lambert, Ettienne Rev. (Box A-71, Folder 244)
    - Lambert, Hendricks & Brown (Box A-71, Folder 245)
      2 prints are stuck together with paste.
    - Lambert, Linda (Box A-71, Folder 246)
    - Lambert, Preston (Box A-71, Folder 247)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Dave Greene, Pope's Studio, Hamilton
    - Lambert, Thomas D. (Box A-71, Folder 248)
    - Lambeth, Charlotte (Box A-71, Folder 249)
    - Lambie, Nat (Box A-72, Folder 1)
    - Lambright, M.A. (Box A-72, Folder 2)
    - Lambs, Cabam (Box A-72, Folder 3)
    - Lamda Kappa Mu (Box A-72, Folder 4)
    - Lamming, George (Box A-72, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Neilson
    - Lamond, Carole (Box A-72, Folder 6)
      Press photo on one leaf hole-punched commercial stock, five images total on recto and verso.
    - Lamont, Barbara (Box A-72, Folder 7)
    - Lamont, Basilio (Box A-72, Folder 8)
    - Lamont, Johnson Jazz Group (Box A-72, Folder 9)
    - Lamos, Adrian (Dr. and Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Joseph Merante
    - Lamotta, Jake (Box A-72, Folder 11)
    - La Mothe, Jean (Box A-72, Folder 12)
      Also one 4"x5" black and white negative in envelope
    - La Motta Brothers Orchestra (Box A-72, Folder 13)
    - La Motta, Jacob (Box A-72, Folder 14)
    - Lamotta, Ray (Box A-72, Folder 15)
    - Lampel, Dave (Box A-72, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Bryan D. Hall, Bill Greene
    - Lampel, David (Box A-72, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo
    - Lampel, Gene (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 18)
    - Lampel, A.L. (Rev.) (Box A-72, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: James Campbell
    - Lampkin, Charles (Box A-72, Folder 20)
    - Lampkin, Daisy (Box A-72, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, International News Photos, Continental News Photos, Llewellyn Ransom
    - Lapmkin, Felix (Box A-72, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: G.G.G. Photo Studio
    - Lampkin, Lillian Cross (Box A-72, Folder 23)
    - Lampkin, Lillian C. (Box A-72, Folder 24)
      Photographer if identified: New York City Youth Board, Dummett
    - Lampkin, Phyllis (Box A-72, Folder 25)
    - Lampkin, Raphael (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 26)
    - Lampkin, Russ (Box A-72, Folder 27)
    - Lampkin, William (Box A-72, Folder 28)
    - Lampley, Calvin (Box A-72, Folder 29)
      Photographer if identified: James Abresch
    - Lampton, George S. (Rev.) (Box A-72, Folder 30)
    - Lancaster, Burt (Box A-72, Folder 31)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photos, Pan American World Airways/Overseas Division/N.Y. International Airport
    - Lancaster, Emmer M. (Box A-72, Folder 32)
      Photographer if identified: Howard University/Office of the Secretary/The Press Service
    - Lancasters, George (Box A-72, Folder 33)
    - Lance, Major (Box A-72, Folder 34)
    - Land, Louis T. (Box A-72, Folder 35)
      Photographer if identified: Sp 5 Bruce Hallowell/First US Army Central Photo Facility/Fort Jay New York 4
    - Lander, Clifton P., Jr. (Box A-72, Folder 36)
    - Lander, Edward (Box A-72, Folder 37)
    - "Landerous" (Box A-72, Folder 38)
    - Landron, Jack (Box A-72, Folder 39)
    - Landrum, Clifford E. (Box A-72, Folder 40)
    - Landrum, Elaine (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 41)
    - Landry, Vera (Box A-72, Folder 42)
    - Landsmark, Ted (Box A-72, Folder 43)
    - Lane, Betty (Box A-72, Folder 44)
    - Lane, Cecil (Box A-72, Folder 45)
    - Lane, Cecelia R. (Box A-72, Folder 46)
    - Lane College (See Hamlett Hall) (Box A-72, Folder 47)
      Photographer if identified: Mark Stansbury
    - Lane, David (Box A-72, Folder 48)
    - Lane, David (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 49)
      Photographer if identified: George West
    - Lane, Debra (Box A-72, Folder 50)
    - Lane, Diane Elise (Box A-72, Folder 51)
    - Lane, Dick (Box A-72, Folder 52)
      Photographer if identified: Laughead Photographers/Dallas TX
    - Lane, Dorothy (Box A-72, Folder 53)
    - Lane, E. Mae (Box A-72, Folder 54)
      Photographer if identified: Frederick H. Simmons
    - Lane, Elnora (Box A-72, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: The Browns
    - Lane, Hugh (Box A-72, Folder 56)
    - Lane, Jeff (Box A-72, Folder 57)
      Photographer if identified: Billy Pierce
    - Lane, Jeff (Box A-72, Folder 58)
    - Lane, Lois Alexander (Box A-72, Folder 59)
      Also one issue of the 16-leaf, black and white printed Harlem Institute of Fashion "souvenir journal and news letter." Also two velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert/News Voice International, Tex Harris, George W. Martin, James Gilbert, Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 19
    - Lane, May (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 60)
    - Lane, Nancy (Box A-72, Folder 61)
    - Lane, Paul (Box A-72, Folder 62)
      Photographer if identified: Wilson
    - Lane, Robert B. (Box A-72, Folder 63)
    - Lane, Thomas (Box A-72, Folder 64)
    - Lane, Tommy (Box A-72, Folder 65)
    - Lane, Perry (Box A-72, Folder 66)
    - Lane, Virginia (Box A-72, Folder 67)
    - Lang, Troy (Box A-72, Folder 68)
      With cv attached by paperclip.
    - Langdon, Clement (and daughter) (Box A-72, Folder 69)
    - Lange, Gerri (Box A-72, Folder 70)
    - Lange, Ted (Box A-72, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: CBS Television Photo Division
    - Langely, Lola (Box A-72, Folder 72)
    - Langford, Elise (Box A-72, Folder 73)
    - Langford, Gilbert B. (Box A-72, Folder 74)
    - Langhart, Janet (Box A-72, Folder 75)
      Including one cut-out photo
    - Langhorne, Emily (Box A-72, Folder 76)
    - Langhorne, Victor (Box A-72, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: Richard Lee
    - Langston, Rikki (Box A-72, Folder 78)
    - Lanier, Joel L. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 79)
    - Lanier, Willie (Box A-72, Folder 80)
    - Lanier, Art (Box A-72, Folder 81)
    - Lanier, Bob (Box A-72, Folder 82)
    - Lanier, Sandra (Miss) (Box A-72, Folder 83)
      With single-leaf caption affixed to verso, caption has badly darkened.
    - Lanier, William (Box A-72, Folder 84)
    - Lanthripp, Maria (Box A-72, Folder 85)
    - Lapeyrolerie, Frank (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 86)
    - La Place, Malcolm (Box A-72, Folder 87)
      Photographer if identified: Del Ankers
    - La Prince (Box A-72, Folder 88)
    - Lapansky, Emma (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 89)
    - La K Fashions (Box A-72, Folder 90)
    - Lark, Raymond (Box A-72, Folder 91)
    - Larkin, Milton (Box A-72, Folder 92)
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Harris Photo
    - Larkin, Tippy (Box A-72, Folder 93)
    - Larkins, Ellis (Box A-72, Folder 94)
    - Larkins, John (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 95)
    - La Rocque Bey (See: Bey, La Rocque) (Box A-72, Folder 96)
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Yearwood, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Larks, The (Box A-72, Folder 97)
    - Larmond, Daphne (Box A-72, Folder 98)
    - Larrier, Hilda (Box A-72, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams
    - Larrier, Othneil (Box A-72, Folder 100)
    - Larry, Delores (Box A-72, Folder 101)
    - Lary and Tina (Box A-72, Folder 102)
    - Larter, Dennis (Box A-72, Folder 103)
    - La Salle, Denise (Box A-72, Folder 104)
    - La Sane, Charlotte (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 105)
    - La'Shannon, Daria (Box A-72, Folder 106)
    - Lashlay, Ezra (Box A-72, Folder 107)
    - Lashley, Dorothy (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 108)
    - Lashley, James (Bishop) (Box A-72, Folder 109)
    - Lasley, Ezra (Box A-72, Folder 110)
      Also one-leaf typescript release attached with paperclip.
    - Lasley, Maria (Box A-72, Folder 111)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Syndicate
    - Lassitor, Betty (Box A-72, Folder 112)
    - Lassiter, Cleveland (Box A-72, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: Syl-Ru Photo Studio
    - Lassiter, James (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 114)
    - Lassiter, John (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 115)
    - Lassiter, T.G., Jr. (Box A-72, Folder 116)
    - Last Poets, The (Box A-72, Folder 117)
    - "Last Street" (Box A-72, Folder 118)
    - Lateef (Box A-72, Folder 119)
    - Lateef Yusteef (Box A-72, Folder 120)
    - Latham, S.H. and Barbara Jo (Box A-72, Folder 121)
    - Latham, Lydia (Box A-72, Folder 122)
    - Lathan, Stan (Box A-72, Folder 123)
    - Lathan and Thomas Productions (Box A-72, Folder 124)
      Also one three-leaf typescript release attached with paperclip.
    - Latifa, Lois-Chinnery (Box A-72, Folder 125)
    - Latimer, Bettye (Box A-72, Folder 126)
    - Latimer, Milton (Box A-72, Folder 127)
      Photographer if identified: Bunny Photo Studio, James Gilbert
    - Lato, Theresa (Box A-72, Folder 128)
    - LaTour, Lou (Box A-72, Folder 129)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix. Also one folded, black and white printed promotional poster with images, illustrations, and bio, attached to two prints with paperclips.
    - LaTour, Nick (Box A-72, Folder 130)
      Also one single-leaf bio and cv, with typescript verso and ms. recto.
    - Lattemore, Everett (Box A-72, Folder 131)
    - Lattimer, Eugene D. (Box A-72, Folder 132)
      Also one two-leaf typescript release and one single-leaf carbon typescript release, both attached to prints.
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.C. Housing Authority
    - Lattimer, Eugene (Box A-72, Folder 133)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y.C. Housing Authority, Cecil Layne
    - Lattemore, George (see Everett) (Box A-72, Folder 134)
    - Lattino, Thryll, Tracy, and Mike (Box A-72, Folder 135)
    - Lattisaw, Stacy (Box A-72, Folder 136)
    - LaTour, Lou (See LuTour, Lou) (Box A-72, Folder 137)
    - Latty, Louise (Ms.) (Box A-72, Folder 138)
    - Lauder, Clifford (Rev.) (Box A-72, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: News Voice International
    - Laughinghouse, Charles (Box A-72, Folder 140)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Columbia University/Sports Information Office
    - Laughton, Gloria (Box A-72, Folder 141)
    - Lauren, Ralph (Box A-72, Folder 142)
    - Lauricella, Thomas A., Jr. (Box A-72, Folder 143)
    - Laury, Patricia A. (Box A-72, Folder 144)
    - Lautier, Louis R. (Box A-72, Folder 145)
      Photographer if identified: International News Photo/A Unit of King Features Synd.
    - Lavester, Kimberly (Box A-72, Folder 146)
    - Laviscount, Julia Pettit-Young (Box A-72, Folder 147)
    - La Vong, R. Nelson "Reggie" (Box A-72, Folder 148)
    - La Voguette (Box A-72, Folder 149)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley Photographer
    - Law, John (Box A-72, Folder 150)
    - Law, Joyce (Box A-72, Folder 151)
    - Law, T.M. (Box A-72, Folder 152)
      Photographer if identified: Ray Hash
    - Lawford, Peter (Box A-72, Folder 153)
    - Lawlin, Theodore K. (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 154)
    - Lawlor, Evelyn (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 155)
      Photographer if identified: Paul Caramuto
    - Lawlor, Evelyn Davis (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 156)
    - Lawnside (Box A-72, Folder 157)
    - Lawrence, Aaron (Box A-72, Folder 158)
    - Lawrence, Alfred (Box A-72, Folder 159)
    - Lawrence, Anderson C. (Box A-72, Folder 160)
    - Lawrence, Barbara (Box A-72, Folder 161)
      Photographer if identified: Henry Monroe
    - Lawrence, Benjamin, Sr. (Box A-72, Folder 162)
    - Lawrence, Carl Dunbar (Box A-72, Folder 163)
      Also one strip of black and white 6"x6" negatives, three frames, in an envelope. Also one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, L. St. Clair Dummett, Nichols, Cleveland Davies
    - Lawrence, Charles (Box A-72, Folder 164)
    - Lawrence, Charles B. (Box A-72, Folder 165)
    - Lawrence, Charles R. (Dr.) (Box A-72, Folder 166)
    - Lawrence, Eddie (Box A-72, Folder 167)
      With newspaper clipping affixed to verso with tape.
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne/Negro Press Services Inc.
    - Lawrence, Geoffrey (Box A-72, Folder 168)
    - Lawrence, George (Dr. and Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 169)
    - Lawrence, George R. (Box A-72, Folder 170)
    - Lawrence, Harvey (Box A-72, Folder 171)
    - Lawrence, Henry (Box A-72, Folder 172)
      Photographer if identified: Fred Thomas
    - Lawrence, Jacob (Box A-72, Folder 173)
    - Lawrence, Jacob (Box A-72, Folder 174)
    - Lawrence, Jacob (Mrs.) (Box A-72, Folder 175)
    - Lawrence, John (Box A-72, Folder 176)
      Photographer if identified: Ulysses Allen Providence
    - Lawrence, Lincoln (Box A-72, Folder 177)
    - Lawrence, Mitty (Box A-72, Folder 178)
      Also identified as "Mittie Lawrence" on verso of prints.
    - Lawrence, Nancy V. (Box A-72, Folder 179)
    - Lawrence, Neil (Box A-72, Folder 180)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Dave Greene
    - Lawrence, Robert H., Jr. (Box A-72, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photos, Wide World Photos
    - Lawrence, Sara M. (Box A-72, Folder 182)
    - Lawrence, Sarah Ware (Box A-72, Folder 183)
      Photographer if identified: Platnick's Photo Service
    - Lawrence, Toni (Box A-72, Folder 184)
      Photographer if identified: Jaime, Harris Photo
    - Lawrence, Tony (Box A-72, Folder 185)
      Eleven prints with single-leaf typescript releases attached with paperclips or staples through border.
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos Inc., Big M, George West, Ross Photos, Popsie, TWA, Gill Photographers
      Number of Prints: 32
    - Lawrence, Ulysses (Box A-72, Folder 186)
    - Lawrence, Yari (Box A-72, Folder 187)
    - Laws, Debra (Box A-72, Folder 188)
    - Laws, Donna (Box A-72, Folder 189)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Dawson
    - Laws, Eloise (Box A-72, Folder 190)
    - Laws, Hubert (Box A-72, Folder 191)
    - Laws, R.A. (Rev.) (Box A-72, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: Rufus Merritt, Dave Greene
    - Laws, Robert and Alexandra (Box A-72, Folder 193)
    - Laws, Ronnie (Box A-72, Folder 194)
    - Laws, Sam (Box A-72, Folder 195)
    - Lawson, Alfred (Box A-72, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: Jimmie Mannas
    - Lawson, Ann (Box A-72, Folder 197)
      One black and white Polaroid print.
    - Lawson, Ayana (Box A-72, Folder 198)
    - Lawson, Behane (Box A-72, Folder 199)
    - Lawson, Atty Belford V. (Box A-72, Folder 200)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, W. Smith, Scurlock
    - Lawson, Ben (Box A-72, Folder 201)
      Commercial printed promo image.
    - Lawson, Cassell (Box A-72, Folder 202)
    - Lawson, David (Box A-72, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Martin Gross
    - Lawson, Doc (Box A-72, Folder 204)
    - Lawson, Edward (Box A-72, Folder 205)
    - Lawson, Harold M. (Box A-72, Folder 206)
    - Lawson, Irene (Box A-72, Folder 207)
      Photographer if identified: Don Ramsay
    - Lawson, James R. (Box A-72, Folder 208)
      One single-leaf typescript cv. One five-leaf carbon typescript letter from Lawson to Mayoral candidate John Lindsay, detailing recommendations for securing the black vote, marked "PRIVATE & CONFIDENTIAL." One five-leaf typescript letter published by the Harlem Council for Economic Development to the Amsterdam News, outlining their program, with envelope attached with staple. One three-leaf typescript report to the Executive Board of Local 669 CIO of UAW. One three-leaf typescript copy of a 1951 talk delivered at Columbia University. One two-sided flier promoting Lawson's candidacy for president of Harlem Labor Union. Also one three-leaf typescript copy of Harlem Council for Economic Development's News Bulletin (#118). One single-leaf photocopy of a thank-you letter from US Senator James L. Buckley to James Lawson. One two-leaf typescript copy of Harlem Council for Economic Development's Weekly Bulletin (May 1964). One two-leaf typescript copy of a speech delivered by James Lawson on AFRICAN UNITY DAY (May 28 1964). One two-leaf typescript release announcing an Ethiopian Princess becoming God Mother of Lawson's baby. One seven-leaf ms. letter or speech defending Lawson from detractors (paper has badly yellowed). One typescript letter from Department of State to Lawson. Approximately five loose newspaper clippings.
    - Lawson, James R. (Box A-72, Folder 209)